{"showBridgeTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40134/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40134,"taskName":"Sauna - Install","taskDescription":"Install a Sauna","xmTaskDescriptor":"Sauna Builders","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Sauna hot tub saunas steam","textMessagingName":"Install Sauna","rolloverLongDesc":"An air- \u0026 moisture-tight room set up for people to sit immersed in deep clouds of steam. Requires heat source \u0026 often a water source \u0026 may involve gas lines, electrical wiring \u0026 plumbing. This category is for installing a sauna or for completely replacing an old one.","rolloverShortDesc":"For therapeutic steam baths.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a Sauna.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Home Sauna Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Build a Sauna","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":45,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Sauna Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Sauna - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Sauna Project","urlName":"Sauna-Install","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home Sauna Installation Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Sauna,hot,tub,saunas,steam,room,spa,jacuzzi","emcCategoryOid":-12044,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":445,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"taskHeader":"Sauna Builders","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40134/":{"taskOID":40134,"originalTaskOID":40134,"setID":445,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1241,"questionDisplayText":"Sauna type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select which type of sauna you would like.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4872,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Precut sauna package available in standard sizes","answerDisplayText":"Precut sauna package available in standard sizes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1769,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Custom sauna made to your specific recommendations","answerDisplayText":"Custom sauna made to your specific recommendations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1242,"questionDisplayText":"Capacity","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many persons would you like to accommodate in your sauna?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6545,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Two","answerDisplayText":"Two","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6560,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two to four","answerDisplayText":"Two to four","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2485,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Five to six","answerDisplayText":"Five to six","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3945,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than six","answerDisplayText":"More than six","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4926,"questionDisplayText":"Sauna location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where will the sauna be located?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3211,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Indoors","answerDisplayText":"Indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4483,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1241,"questionDisplayText":"Sauna type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select which type of sauna you would like.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4872,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Precut sauna package available in standard sizes","answerDisplayText":"Precut sauna package available in standard sizes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1769,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Custom sauna made to your specific recommendations","answerDisplayText":"Custom sauna made to your specific recommendations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4872,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Precut sauna package available in standard sizes","answerDisplayText":"Precut sauna package available in standard sizes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1769,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Custom sauna made to your specific recommendations","answerDisplayText":"Custom sauna made to your specific recommendations","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1242,"questionDisplayText":"Capacity","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many persons would you like to accommodate in your sauna?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6545,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Two","answerDisplayText":"Two","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6560,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two to four","answerDisplayText":"Two to four","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2485,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Five to six","answerDisplayText":"Five to six","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3945,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than six","answerDisplayText":"More than six","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6545,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Two","answerDisplayText":"Two","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6560,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two to four","answerDisplayText":"Two to four","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2485,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Five to six","answerDisplayText":"Five to six","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3945,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than six","answerDisplayText":"More than six","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4926,"questionDisplayText":"Sauna location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where will the sauna be located?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3211,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Indoors","answerDisplayText":"Indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4483,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3211,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Indoors","answerDisplayText":"Indoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4483,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}